Guide to the Bob Berenson Papers, 1950-2004 and undated RL.11101
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Manila File, 1950-2002 and undated; 1
  - 302. American Households of the 1990s, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 303. Integration of Direct Marketing and Sales Promotion, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 304. Current Advertiser Practices in Compensating Their Advertising Agencies, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 305. Tom Wolfe, Aspirations of an American Century, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 306. American Households of the 1990s, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 307. Creative Strategy examples, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 307a. Creative Strategy examples, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 308. J. Walker Smith, Marketers' Perceptions of the Marketing Process in the Eighties, 1987 (Box 8)
  - 309. Andrall Pearson, Six Basics for General Managers, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 310. The Business of New Business, 1989 (Box 8)
  - 311. Marketing to the Small Businessman, 1988 (Box 8)
  - 312. Helen Galland, Changes in the World of Retailing Today, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 313. Problems facing retailers, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 314. Micro-marketing, Stalking the New Consumer, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 315. John Philip Jones, Cure the Industry with More Creativity, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 316. Murray Gross, Supermarkets: New Battlefield, New Opportunity, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 317. The Value of a Brand, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 318. Tracy Carlson, I Am the Very Model of a Manager of Marketing, undated (Box 9)
  - 319. Communications Industry Forecast 1989-1993 (Box 9)
  - 320. H.E. McDonald, The Great Uneven Agency Playing Field, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 321. JWT Summary of Brand Strategy, undated (Box 9)
  - 322. Roger Clayton, Whole Brain presentation, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 323. JWT Consumer's Buying System, undated (Box 9)
  - 324. MIT Study: Management in the 1990s, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 325. Growing Revenue in Media and Communications Businesses, undated (Box 9)
  - 326. Brian Dumaine, P, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 326a. John Paul Newport Jr., American Express: Service that Sells, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 327. Edward Meyer, Getting Back to Basics, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 328. Larry Chiagouris and Leslie Perrell, Asking the Right Questions, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 329. Market-Driven Communications: Best Practices (IBM), 1989 (Box 9)
  - 330. How to Double or Triple Productivity, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 331. Go for It: A Guide to Careers in Advertising, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 332. Edward Meyer, NRMA speech, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 333. Grey publicity, 1956-1969 (Box 9)
  - 334. Barbara Feigin, Videocart speech, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 335. John Philip Jones, Ad Spending: Maintaining Market Share, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 336. James Schroer, Ad Spending: Growing Market Share, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 337. AAAA, Negotiating Agency Compensation, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 338. Consumer Advertising: Diversification Begets Integration, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 339. Ben Stein, Human Capital, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 340. Building Mars' Marketing Power for the 90s, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 341. Len Gross, How to Be a More Effective Account Manager, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 342. King Customer, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 343. Lisbeth Schorr, Raising the Odds of Children's Success, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 344. AAAA, Negotiating Agency Compensation, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 345. Robert Buzzell, The Costly Bargain of Trade Promotion, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 346. Henry Mintzberg, The Manager's Job: Folklore and Fact, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 347. Broadview, Selling Your Company, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 348. Broadview, Mergers and Acquisitions of Information Services Companies for 1989, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 349. Allan Baldinger, Defining and Applying the Brand Equity Concept, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 350. AAAA, Compensation in the Nineties, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 351. Norma Rosenberg, How to Prepare a Business Plan, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 352. A Brand is a Curious Beast, undated (Box 10)
  - 353. JWT, Write if You Want Work, undated (Box 10)
  - 354. Charles Garfield, Peak Performers vs. Workaholics, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 355. Building Mars' Marketing Power for the 90s, 1989 (Box 10)
  - 356. Roger Edwards, International marketing speech, 1989 (Box 10)
  - 357. Saatchi Saatchi creative philosophy, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 358. Advertising Spending, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 359. Magid Abraham and Leonard Lodish, Getting the Most Out of Advertising and Promotion, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 360. Patricia Sellers, What Consumers Really Want, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 361. Advertising Spending, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 362. JWT, Write if You Want Work, undated (Box 10)
  - 363. Managing the agency financially, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 364. James Fallows, Containing Japan, 1989 (Box 10)
  - 365. Some Thoughts on Client Profitability, undated (Box 10)
  - 366. Jack Frantz, Managing Account Management People, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 367. Chiat/Day/Mojo creative development, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 368. Philip Geier, Opportunities and Problems Facing the Global Advertising Business, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 369. Conference Board, Creating Customer Satisfaction, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 370. Grey research techniques, 1971-1990 (Box 10)
  - 371. Bridge-Building Marketing, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 372. Grey's Approach to New Products, 1987 (Box 10)
  - 373. Grey's Philosophy of Brand Character, 1987 (Box 10)
  - 374. IBM strategic presentation, 1988 (Box 10)
  - 375. Howard Shank, How to Retire Without Going Crazy, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 376. John Philip Jones, The Double Jeopardy of Sales Promotions, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 377. Advertising Council, Breaking the Cycle of Disadvantage, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 378. Public Pulse, 31 Major Trends Shaping the Future of American Business, undated (Box 10)
  - 379. Communications Consistency, undated (Box 10)
  - 380. Market by Market Planning, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 381. Radio: Grey's Perspective, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 382. Carolyn Carter, Speech to women in communication, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 383. AAAA, A Practical Solution to Client-Agency Account Conflicts, 1988 (Box 10)
  - 384. Deep Thinker: How Not to Build a Firm, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 385. Andy Zipser, Mad as in Madison Avenue, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 386. George Weidemann, Personal Marketing When the Customer Talks Back, 1987 (Box 10)
  - 387. Judith Waldrop, You'll Know the 21st Century when..., 1990 (Box 10)
  - 388. Don Schultz, Integrating Marketing Communications in an Age of Specialization, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 389. A Strategic Branding Model for Maximum Business Growth, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 390. Television production, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 391. Regis McKenna, Marketing is Everything, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 392. Peter McWilliams, How to Publish Your Own Book, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 393. Agency compensation, undated (Box 10)
  - 394. AAAA, Advertising in a Recession, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 395. APC breakfast correspondence (humor), 1973 (Box 10)
  - 396. Grey Travel and Entertainment Policies and Procedures, 1990 (Box 10)
  - 397. Hilton Grey UK Retail Center, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 398. Advertising in a recession, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 399. Russell Haley and Allan Baldinger, The ARF Copy Research Validity Project, 1991 (Box 10)
  - 400. The Customer-Driven Company, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 401. Alec Gerster, The New Media World, undated (Box 11)
  - 402. Mark Landler, What's in a Name? Less and Less, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 403. Alec Gerster, Who Should Buy Your Media? The Case for Full Service Agencies, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 404. Nancy Sutton, Commencement speech at Allegheny College, 1990 (Box 11)
  - 405. AAAA, Advertising in a Recession, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 406. The Purest Treasure, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 407. Barbara Feigin, The Role of Agency Research Departments, 1988 (Box 11)
  - 408. Agency without Walls: Mixing and Matching at Grey, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 409. Integrated marketing communications articles, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 410. Discussion with Wal-Mart, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 411. Survey of National Consumer Goods Advertisers, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 412. Gretchen Morgenson, The Trend is Not Their Friend, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 413. Mark Landler, What Happened to Advertising?, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 414. AAAA, It Works! How Investment Spending in Advertising Pays Off, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 415. Barbara Feigin, Tough Times, Tougher Customers: No More Business as Usual, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 416. Price Pritchett, The Ethics of Excellence, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 417. John F. Mars, The Five Principles of Mars, undated (Box 11)
  - 418. Discussion with Wal-Mart, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 419. Presentation to ConAgra Frozen Foods, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 420. Clients and Categories with Additional Business Opportunities for Grey Advertising, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 421. AAAA, It Works! How Investment Spending in Advertising Pays Off, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 422. Grey, Ten Observations on Financial Management, undated (Box 11)
  - 423. Edwin Artzt, Grooming the Next Generation of Management, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 424. Wall Street Journal, Why Advertise?, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 425. Smith Barney, Advertising/Marketing Services, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 426. Integrated Marketing Communications reprints, 1991 (Box 11)
  - 427. Michael Moore, Media-Buying Consortia: They Can't Happen Here--Or Can They?, 1992 (Box 11)
  - 428. Robert Berenson, What Makes Advertising Great?, undated (Box 11)
  - 429. Robert Berenson, What Makes Advertising Great?, 1992 (Box 11)
  - 430. Tough Times, Tougher Customers: No More Business as Usual, 1992 (Box 11)
  - 431. AAAA, Real Ad Spending and Its Effect on Market Share, 1992 (Box 11)
  - 432. Grey Brand Character Advertising Philosophy, undated (Box 11)
  - 433. George Salk, Competing on Capabilities: The New Rules of Corporate Strategy, 1992 (Box 11)
  - 434. Robert Berenson, What's Happening in the World of Packaged Goods Marketing?, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 435. The Age of Interactive TV, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 436. Ambassador Program speech reference book, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 437. Speech 1: Censorship is Contagious: You, Advertising and the First Amendment, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 438. Speech 2: Changing Portraits: The Image of Women and Men in Advertising, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 439. Speech 3: Ethics and Advertising: A Moral Compass, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 440. Speech 4: Everything You Wanted to Know about Advertising But Couldn't Find Anybody to Ask, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 441. Speech 5: Television Advertising: It's No Longer Black and White, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 442. Speech 6: The Bottom Line is Helping People, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 443. Modules of Ambassador Program, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 444. Module 1: Advertising Self-Regulation, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 445. Module 2: Advertising Tax, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 446. Module 3: Advertising to Children, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 447. Module 4: Alcohol Advertising, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 448. Module 5: Political Advertising, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 449. Module 6: Special Markets: Advertising to Minorities, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 450. Module 7: Subliminal Advertising, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 451. Module 8: Tobacco Advertising, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 452. How to Evaluate Place-Based Media, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 453. Joan Walker, The New Business of Advertising, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 454. Building Great Advertising with Brand Character, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 455. Alvin Achenbaum, Craps or Poker: Gambling on New Market Entries, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 456. Grey Europe, Middle East and Africa Management Meeting, 1991 (Box 12)
  - 457. Nancy Salz, Salz Survey of Advertiser-Agency Relations, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 458. Never Lose Another Client!, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 459. Grey historical timeline, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 460. Kids Media Marketplace, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 461. Interviews with former Grey employees, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 462. W. Chan Kim and Renee Maybaurgne, Parables of Leadership, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 463. Grey Europe, Middle East and Africa Management Meeting, 1991 (Box 12)
  - 464. Christopher Power, Will It Sell in Podunk? Hard to Say, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 465. The Purest Treasure, 1991 (Box 12)
  - 466. Edith Weiner, What Does the Future Hold: Trends of and for the 90s, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 467. Todd Garrett, Globalization and Its Significance to P, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 468. Barbara Feigin, The Future is Now: Maintaining Your Edge in a Changing Marketplace, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 469. Robert Lauterborn, Accountability, Budgets and Compensation Systems, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 470. Thomas Bonoma, How to Be a CEO, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 471. James R. Wills Jr., Winning New Business: An Analysis of Advertising Agency Activities, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 472. David Aaker, Managing Brand Equity (excerpts), undated (Box 12)
  - 473. Grey credentials, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 474. Bob Schoenfein, Seven Deadly Sins of Credentials Presentations, 1990 (Box 12)
  - 475. Robert Berenson, How to Sell Your Big Creative Idea, Every Time, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 476. Robert Berenson, Great Advertising Doesn't Just Happen, 1992 (Box 12)
  - 477. Disney Institute, 1992 (Box 13)
  - 478. Topic for discussion at AAAA informal board meeting, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 479. Barbara Feigin, The New Rules of the Game: How to Win in Today's Marketplace, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 480. Coalition for Brand Equity progress report, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 481. Barbara Feigin and Stephen Novick, The Brand Contract: A New Business-Building Tool for the 90s, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 482. Promotion and Perks, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 483. Peter Glen, Resolutions for New Realities, 1991 (Box 13)
  - 484. Stuart Sanders, Prospect Personality Profiling: Chemistry, Not Creative Wins New Business, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 485. Ron Fierman, Renegotiating Compensation with Current Clients, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 486. General Foods compensation conversation, 1992 (Box 13)
  - 487. Alec Gerster, The Empowered Viewer, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 488. Our New Business Challenge: Our Solution, Your Goal, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 489. Grey Europe, Middle East and Africa management meeting, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 490. Brands on Trial (Adweek), 1993 (Box 13)
  - 491. The Ultimate Rejection (humor), undated (Box 13)
  - 492. A Few Random Thoughts about Media and Where It's Going, undated (Box 13)
  - 493. Morgan Stanley, Private Label vs. Branded Products: A Marketing Revolution, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 494-497 folders missing (Box 13)
  - 498. Edwin Artzt, The Future of Advertising, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 499. Milt Weinstock, Brand equity presentation to Cadbury, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 500. Barbara Feigin, High-Tech, High-Touch, Higher Sales: Relationship Marketing, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 501. Margaret Henderson Blair and Karl Rosenberg, Convergent Findings Increase Our Understanding of How Advertising Works, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 502. GTFH Management Vision, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 503. Bates USA, These Prices Are Killing Us: What Brand-Driven Marketing Must Do to Combat Price-Driven Competition, undated (Box 13)
  - 504. Dick Martin, The Executive's Guide to Handling a Press Interview, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 505. Edward Meyer, Staying Ahead of the Curve: New Trends in Advertising, 1994 (Box 13)
  - 506-521. The Ambassador Program, 1 of 4, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 506-521. The Ambassador Program, 2 of 4, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 506-521. The Ambassador Program, 3 of 4, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 506-521. The Ambassador Program, 4 of 4, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 522. Larry Light, Building Brand Relationships, 1993 (Box 13)
  - 523. Leo Burnett, Relationship Marketing, 1994 (Box 14)
  - 524. Grey, Agency Compensation and Client Negotiation, 1988 (Box 14)
  - 525. Texaco Globalization, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 526. Grey Responds to Mars, Incorporated Advertising Agency Review, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 527. Milt Weinstock, Before Anything...The Idea, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 528. Kid Power Conference, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 529. Eric Miller, The Context of Trends: The Reshaping of America, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 530. Grey London, World Trends in Advertising, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 531. Conference Board, The Changing Global Role of the Marketing Function, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 532. Bob Berenson, Gaining the Competitive Advantage in the New World of Health Care, 1994 (Box 14)
  - 533. Grey Sydney, Insights on the Global Market for RTE Cereal, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 534. How World-Class Marketers Stay that Way: Going Beyond Ideas, Demanding Insights, undated (Box 14)
  - 535. Celebrity worth in advertising, 1987-1995 (Box 14)
  - 536. Strategic vision articles, 1993 (Box 14)
  - 537. Advertising's Role in Building Brand Equity, 1993 (Box 14)
  - 538. Tom Teran, Building Brand Equity in the Age of Consumer Pragmatism, 1994 (Box 14)
  - 539. DDB Needham corporate handbook, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 540. Grey update of international countries 1990-1995 (Box 14)
  - 541. Getting the Best from Your Agency Resources, 1995 (Box 14)
  - 542. Spotlight, article on Dick Karp, 1987 (Box 14)
  - 543. Pan Pacific Consortium, Nothing in Common?, 1987 (Box 14)
  - 544. Larry Light, Brand Loyalty Marketing; John Philip Jones, Does Advertising Produce Sales Today or Sales Tomorrow?, 1994 (Box 14)
  - 545. Lee Anne Morgan, Organizing for the Betterment of the Brand, 1997 (Box 14)
  - 546. Shelley Lazarus, Positioning the Agency as a Brand, 1997 (Box 14)
  - 547. Niall FitzGerald, The Need for Duality, 1997. (Box 15)
  - 548. Bopb Schoenfein, Guide for New Business Presentations, 1997 (Box 15)
  - 549. Organizing for Global Competitiveness, 1996 (Box 15)
  - 550. Managing the New Chase Corporate Brand, 1996 (Box 15)
  - 551. John Kotter, Leading Change: Why Transformation Efforts Fail, 1995 (Box 15)
  - 552. Tough Times, Tougher Customers: The Changing American Mindset, undated (Box 15)
  - 553. Wendy Lurie, Qualitative skills workshop, 1998 (Box 15)
  - 554. Barbara Feigin, The Power of Positioning in Creating Brand Value, 1998 (Box 15)
  - 555. Mike Becker, Observations, undated (Box 15)
  - 556. Saatchi Saatchi, Lovemarks, 2001 (Box 15)
  - 557. Brendon Ryan, Hey, This Stuff Actually Works!, 2002 (Box 15)
  - 558. Carolyn Carter, Premium by Design, 2002 (Box 15)
- Office Files, 1988-2004 and undated; 2
  - AAE (Assistant Account Executive) seminars, 1993-2002 (Box 15)
  - AEF (Advertising Educational Foundation), 2004 (Box 15)
  - AEF-VPP (Advertising Educational Foundation-Visiting Professor Program), 2002-2004 (Box 15)
  - Agilent presentation, 2002 (Box 16)
  - Ambassador Program, 1998-1999 (Box 16)
  - ANA (Association of National Advertisers) presentation, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Assistant Media Planners presentations, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Borden's--Credentials presentation, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Brand equity, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Brand globalization (Texaco), 1995 (Box 16)
  - Brands under Attack, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Business 2.0 magazine, 1999 (Box 16)
  - CEO dialogue, 2000 (Box 16)
  - Challenges to the Advertising Agencies--AAAA Board meeting, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Chase--Credentials (Kevin McCabe), 1993 (Box 16)
  - Columbia University presentation, 1998 (Box 16)
  - Columbia University presentation, 1999 (Box 16)
  - Competitive Branding Systems, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Downshifting in America, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Edison Awards presentation, 1997 (Box 17)
  - FAST (Future of Advertising Stakeholders) Summit speech, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Great Advertising Doesn't Just Happen (Barbara Feigin), 1988 (Box 17)
  - Great Advertising Doesn't Just Happen--Brand Character: Grey's Secret Weapon, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Great Advertising Doesn't Just Happen--Columbia University, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Great Advertising Doesn't Just Happen--MIT, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Great Advertising Doesn't Just Happen--Syracuse University, 1994 (Box 17)
  - Grey Direct presentation, 1997 (Box 17)
  - Grey Interactive: Building a Global Interactive Network in a Global Medium, 1997 (Box 17)
  - How to Sell Your Big Idea, Every Time, 1996 (Box 17)
  - Index to bookshelf, undated (Box 18)
  - International Week, 1992 (Box 18)
  - International Week speech, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Internet advertising, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Internet seminar, 2000 (Box 18)
  - Jim McConnell, New business presentation: How to Win by Not Losing, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Leigh Bureau speaker list, 1992 (Box 18)
  - MAIP (Multicultural Advertising Intern Program?) presentation, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Management breakfast talk, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Media buyers and planners presentation, 1999 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1998-1999 (Box 18)
  - NetBits Beyond Interactive training seminar, 2000 (Box 18)
  - New Snack/Pringles presentation, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Northwestern University presentation, 1998 (Box 18)
  - Raise policy script, 1992 (Box 18)
  - Roger Edwards--Advertising trends BAT presentation, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Roger Edwards--Advertising trends BAT presentation, 1993 (Box 19)
  - State of Grey and Outlook for the Future, 1991 (Box 19)
  - Tough Times, Tougher Customers (Barbara Feigin), 1991 (Box 19)
  - Unisys presentation--B2B best practices, 2004 (Box 19)
  - What Makes Great Advertising Great?, 2004 (Box 20)
  - What's Happening in the World of Packaged Goods Marketing?--Fairfield University, 1992 (Box 20)
  - When Clients Drive You Crazy (Warren Berger), 1999 (Box 20)
  - World Trends in Advertising (Roger Edwards), 1994 (Box 20)
  - Worldwide Week, 1994- (Box 20)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1997-2004; 3
  - AAE Seminar, 2000 (Box 21)
  - CEO Dialogue May 11 2000 (Box 21)
  - Grey Craft Reel, 1998 (Box 21)
  - Hot Grey, 1998 (Box 21)
  - Media Buyers and Planners Presentation, 1999 (Box 21)
  - Showreel, 2003 (Box 21)
  - Berkeley presentation, 2004 (Box 21)
  - Grey presentation reel, 2004 (Box 21)
  - VPP Reel, 2003 (Box 21)
  - What Makes Great Advertising, 2004 (Box 21)
  - Columbia Presentation, 1998 (Box 21)
  - MIT Presentation, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Northwestern University Craft Reel, 1998 (Box 21)
  - University of California at Berkeley Presentation March 10, 2004 (Box 21)
  - What Makes Great Advertising, 2004 (Box 21)
  - B2B Marketing Presentation, 2004 (Box 21)
  - University of California at Berkeley Presentation March 10, 2004 (Box 21)